{
    "subject": "resource/Stoof_Bezuidenhout",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1986_births",
    "human_readable": "Stoof Bezuidenhout is a subject of the 1986 births category.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9877419471740723,
            "question": "Is Stoof Bezuidenhout a subject of the 1986 births?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8159992694854736,
            "question": "To which category does Stoof Bezuidenhout belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7898200750350952,
            "question": "In what year was Stoof Bezuidenhout born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7649533152580261,
            "question": "Who is Stoof Bezuidenhout?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7504693865776062,
            "question": "What year marks Stoof Bezuidenhout's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7089095711708069,
            "question": "What can we learn about Stoof Bezuidenhout from his birth year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3989941477775574,
            "question": "How might someone born in 1986 be influenced by the events of that year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3495836555957794,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about people born in 1986?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2578572630882263,
            "question": "Are there any notable events that occurred in 1986?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08830844610929489,
            "question": "What are some common characteristics of people born in the same year?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Stoof Bezuidenhout is a subject of the 1986 births category.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1333_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable events that occurred in 1986?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1333_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about people born in 1986?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1333_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might someone born in 1986 be influenced by the events of that year?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1333_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1333_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1333_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1333_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1333_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1333_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1333_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1333_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1333_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1333_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1333_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries!"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The context information provided includes details about someone born on May 10, 1986, which aligns with the query stating that Stoof Bezuidenhout is a subject of the 1986 births category."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}